[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Okay.
好
Well instead of the analysis that we just did,
我们先不管之前的分析
we can instead think about modeling the relationship
我们先来思考一下关于这个模型
between the square footage of the house and the house sales price.
房屋价格和房屋面积的关系
And to do this, we're gonna use something that's called linear regression.
关于这个 我们会用到一个叫做线性回归的方法
Okay, so to leverage all the observations that we've collected, what we wanna do is
为了充分发挥所有的收集到的观察样本
be able to understand the relationship between the square foot of the house and
我们要做的是 能够更好地理解 面积和
the house sales price.
房子的出售价格
And so the simplest model we can use for this,
所以说最简单的模型
is just fitting a line through the data.
就是在这些数据中拟合出一条直线
So here's an example of a line fit to this data.
这就是一条拟合出来的直线的例子
And this line is defined by an intercept W0 and a slope W1.
这条直线有着斜率W1和截距W0
And so often we'll talk about W1 being the weight on the feature X or
我们通常把W1叫做特征X的权重
its called the regression coefficient.
也就是回归系数
And what this weight has an interpretation of,
这个权重就是
is as we vary X, the square footage of the house,
不同的X 也就是不同的房屋面积
how much of an impact does that have on changes in the observed house sales price?
它会对观测的房屋价格有多大的影响
Okay, so these two things, our intercept and
这里有两样东西 一个是截距
our slope are the parameters of our model.
一个是斜率 也就是我们模型的参数
And so, to be very explicit here, we're gonna write this function,
为了清楚地表达 我们写下了这样一个函数
this linear function here, with the subscript W,
一个线性函数 这个下标w
that indicates that this function is specified by parameters.
代表着这个函数的参数
W being the set of W0 and W1.
W会是w0 和 w1的一个集合
Okay, so this is the line that we fit through the data.
这是我们通过数据拟合的直线
But a question is, which line is the right line or a good line to use for
那么问题来了 哪一条线是最好的直线
a given data set.
对于这组数据
So maybe we could draw this line or this one instead.
也许我们可以画另一条线呀
And each one of those is given by a different set of parameters w.
每一条线都会代表这不同的一组参数w
And a question is which w do we want to choose for our model?
所以我们的问题就是 如何去选择一组W作为我们模型的参数
Okay, well, to think about this, let's talk about defining a cost for
好了 我们先说一个概念 就是关于
a given line.
给定一条直线 怎么去定义它的
And one very common cost associated with a specific fit to
有一种很常用的拟合方法
the data is something called the residual sum of squares.
那就是通过残差平方和
So, the residual sum of squares, we take our fitted line and
所以说通过取残差平方和的最小值 我们能够得到所要求的拟合直线
we look at each of our observations.
让我们来看样本数据
And we look at how far is that observation
我们看每一个点 离 我们预测的模型的值
from what the model would predict.
到底有多远
Which is just the point on the line.
也就是直线上的点
So we look at all of these distances here, and
让我们看每一个点到直线的距离
we actually look at the square of these distances.
我们其实是在看这些距离的平方和
That's why it's called the residual.
所以也为什么叫做残差
The residual is the difference of your prediction and your actual observation.
因为他表示着你的预测值和真实的数据的值差了多少
We're gonna look at the square and we're going to sum over them.
我们会看这个距离的平方和 并且把他们加起来
Okay, so this is the equation, here more explicitly, where we have the price,
这个就是等式 非常的直观 我们这里有价格
this is our observed house sales price for the first house.
也就是我们第一件房屋的真实售价
And what is this term here?
那么这里的这个因式是什么呢？
So, if this is what I'm calling dollar house one,
恩 就把他叫做房屋价格1吧
then what this point here is,
这个点呢?
is if this is square footage of house one.
这个点代表着  如果这个点 有着一定的面积
Then this x that I've drawn here
就是我现在划出X的这个点
represents exactly this term here.
代表着这一项 (w0+w1*sq.ft house1)^2
This is that value, the point on the line.
所以说这个值就是正好位于我们线上的点
So this dollar sign minus this term here is
所以说 我们房屋价格1减去这边的这一项(w0+w1*sq.ft house1)
the difference between our observed house price versus what our model,
两者之差 就是我们房屋真实售价 和我们模型预测售价
just this line, predicts for this given house square foot.
也就是这条直线 它代表着 对于一定的房屋面积 我们预测的房屋售价
And we're squaring that and
取这两者之差 并且平方它们
we're summing over all the different houses in our data set.
然后把每一个房屋 (观测值) 的两者之差的平方 加起来求和
Okay, so we think about trying to find the best line according to this metric that
所以说  来思考一下 通过这种标准 也就是残差平方和
I've defined here, this residual sum of squares,
找到的最好的拟合直线
what we do is we research over all possible W 0 and W 1.
我们所做的就是 去找到所有可能存在的W0和W1
So all possible lines,
你看 这边就是可能存在的直线
and we choose the one that minimizes the residual sum of squares.
我们在这么多直线中 取一条能够使得残差平方和最小的直线
So we're gonna denote the resulting W as W hat.
所以我们就把这些W最后的结果 叫做 w hat
So remember that's gonna be the set of w hat zero, and w hat one.
所以记住将会有W0的集合，以及W1的集合
Our intercept and our slope.
也就是我们的截距和斜率
Okay.
好
So there exists really nice and efficient algorithms for
这就是我们 计算w hat 有效而简介的算法啦
computing this w hat, this search over all possible ws.
通过去找所有可能存在的ws
We could look at parameters of this model.
我们会去看这个模型的参数
But we're gonna discuss these algorithms more in the regression course.
我们还会在回归课程中讨论这些算法
Ok, so now let's talk about how to take our estimated model parameters and
让我们先来考虑如何去衡量这些参数
use them to predict the value of my house.
并且预测我们房屋的价格吧
So I've gone through, sorry, this star shouldn't be there.
不好意思 这个星星不应该在这里
This should be a hat, just to be clear.
这个应该是 w hat
And I've gone through and plotted the line
我画了一条直线 穿过了这些点
associated with our estimated w0 hat and w1 hat.
也就是用了我们预测的w0 hat 和 w1 hat
And now, here's my house.
恩 这个是我的房子
This is its square footage.
这是它的面积
And the best guess of my house price, is simply what the line predicts.
所以说对于这个面积的房子 来猜测它的价格 也就是这个直线所预测的价格
So I go, and I compute what is the value for this square footage of my house.
所以你看我 就计算出了 我这套房子 这个面积 的价格
Which is W0 hat plus W1 hat times the square footage
也就是w0 hat 加上 w1 hat乘上我的面积数
of my house okay very, very straightforward.
非常简洁明了
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community